Finding Aid for James K. Pollock Papers, 1920-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence 1912-1968, 26 linear feet
  - 1946-1968 1966-1968
    - Sa-Sc 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-21]
    - Se-Sh 1964-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-1]
    - Si-Sp 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-2]
    - St-Su 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-3]
    - T 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-4]
    - U-V 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-5]
    - Wa-Wh 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-6]
    - Wi-Wy 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-7]
    - World Health Foundation 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 30)
      [30-8; 30-9]
    - X-Z 1966-1968 (Box 30)
      [30-10]
- Organizational Affiliations and Professional Interests 1935-1968, 7 linear feet
  Organizational Affiliations and Professional Interests (1935-1968; 7 linear ft.) is a topical file maintained by Pollock for his political science organizational involvement and other miscellaneous professional interests. Included are extensive files for the American Political Science Association, the Governmental Affairs Institute, and the International Political Science Association. Pollock had been a participant in the foundation of the IPSA in 1949, and served as its president from 1955 to 1958. Both the files of this organization and the correspondence between Pollock and its other leaders, particularly in Europe, provide insight into the varying concepts of political science in different countries and the practical uses to which it might be put. The researcher should note that there might be additional materials on these and other organizations in the Correspondence series.
  - American Political Science Association
    - 1950-1951 (Box 30)
      [16-15]
    - 1951-1952 (Box 30)
      [16-14]
    - 1953-1954 (Box 30)
      [16-13]
    - Committee on Reorganization 1951-1952 (Box 30)
      [16-19]
    - Report of the Committee on Relations with Public Officials December 28, 1941 (Box 30)
      [16-16a]
    - Summary list of public service activities of political scientists rendered to governmental agencies 1935-1940, December 1940 (Box 30)
      [16-16b]
  - American Society for Public Administration, Conference of April 5-8, 1961 (Box 30)
    [16-20]
  - Applications for political science teaching fellows and assistants 1955-1958, 2 folders (Box 30)
    [16-17; 16-18]
  - Army
    - Dept. of the Army correspondence 1946-1949 (Box 30)
      [16-21]
    - United States Army War College 1956-1957 (Box 30)
      [16-22]
    - United States Army War College 1957 (Box 30)
      [16-23]
  - Atomic energy: pro-seminar entitled, "Public Policy and Atomic Energy," 1950 (Box 17)
    [17-1]
  - Batt Committee: Advisory Committee on the Problems of the American Public Service of the National Planning Association 1954-1955 (Box 17)
    [17-2a]
  - Bicentennial Conference on Federalism, Columbia University January 1954 (Box 17)
    [17-2b]
  - Brookings Institution-Duke University Conference on International Relations 1949 (Box 17)
    [17-2c]
  - Brookings Institution. Seminar on Problems in U.S. Foreign Policy (Box 17)
    [17-5]
  - Commission on American Government Personnel
    - General 1952-1953 (Box 17)
      [17-3]
    - Paper by Thomas S. Francis entitled, "A Statistical Analysis of Public Service Personnel" undated, circa 1953 (Box 17)
      [17-4]
  - Credit Control. James K. Pollock statement before the Congressional Subcommittee on General Credit Control and Debt Management of the Joint Committee on the Economic Report March 21, 1952 (Box 17)
    [17-7]
  - Detroit Committee on Foreign Relations (Council of Foreign Relations) 1946-1949 (Box 17)
    [17-8]
  - Faculty. "The Evaluation of Faculty Services" Report of a Committee of the University of Michigan Chapter of the AAUP (Box 17)
    [17-9]
  - Ford Foundation 1951-1954 (Box 17)
    [17-10]
  - Ford Foundation 1952-1953 (Box 17)
    [17-11]
  - Germany
    - Correspondence with W. H. Chamberlain, E. A. Mowrer and others regarding Germany 1947-1948 (Box 17)
      [17-12a]
    - German election, summer 1954 (Box 17)
      [17-12b]
    - Residential Seminar on World Politics entitled "The Impact of the New Germany" (Box 17)
      [17-6]
  - Governmental Affairs Institute
    - 1950-1951 (Box 17)
      [17-21]
    - 1952-1953 (Box 17)
      [17-19]
    - 1954-1956 (Box 17)
      [17-18]
    - 1956 (Box 17)
      [17-17]
    - 1957 (Box 17)
      [17-16]
    - 1956-1958 (Box 17)
      [17-14]
    - 1957-1959 (Box 17)
      [17-13]
    - 1958-1959 (Box 17)
      [17-15]
    - Japanese Legislative Services Delegation June 1951 (Box 17)
      [17-20]
    - 1959-1965 (Box 31)
      [31-5]
    - 1965-1966 (Box 31)
      [31-8]
    - 1966 (Box 31)
      [31-4]
    - 1967 (Box 31)
      [31-3]
    - 1968 (Box 31)
      [31-2]
    - Board meeting 1967 (Box 31)
      [31-1]
    - "The World Voter" project 1967-1968 (Box 31)
      [31-6]
    - Foreign Leader Exchange Program (Box 31)
      [31-7]
    - Agenda books
      - 1959-1961 (Box 31)
        [31-10a]
      - 1962-1964 (Box 31)
        [31-9]
  - Institute for Social Studies at the Hague 1953-1954 (Box 31)
    [31-10b]
  - Institute of World Affairs, Riverside, California 1941 (Box 31)
    [31-10c]
  - Institute on Manpower Utilization and Government Personnel 1951 (Box 31)
    [31-10d]
  - International Political Science Association
    - Circular letters 1953-1955 (Box 31)
      [31-11]
    - Stockholm meeting 1955, 4 folders (Box 31)
      [31-12 to 31-15]
    - Correspondence 1953-1955 (Box 31)
      [31-16]
    - Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box 31)
      [31-17]
    - Correspondence with John Goormaghtigh 1955-1956 (Box 31)
      [31-18]
    - Correspondence 1950-1952 (Box 32)
      [32-1]
    - Zurich Conference 1950 (Box 32)
      [32-2]
    - Hague Conference 1952 (Box 32)
      [32-3]
    - Florence Round Table and Meeting 1954 (Box 32)
      [32-4]
    - Round Table 1956 (Box 32)
      [32-5]
    - Rome Congress 1958 (Box 32)
      [32-6]
    - Ann Arbor Round Table 1960
      - General (Box 32)
        [32-7]
      - Correspondence (arranged alphabetically), 3 folders (Box 32)
        [32-8; 32-9; 32-10]
      - Executive Committee Meeting (Box 32)
        [32-11]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 32)
      [32-12]
    - Pittsburgh Round Table 1957 (Box 32)
      [32-13]
    - Correspondence with Rockefeller Foundation 1956-1957 (Box 32)
      [32-14a]
    - Correspondence with Alfred P. Sloan Foundation 1956 (Box 32)
      [32-14b]
    - Correspondence with United Nations Technical Assistance Administration regarding the Local Government Research Project 1957-1958 (Box 32)
      [32-15]
    - UNESCO correspondence 1957-1959 (Box 32)
      [32-16a]
    - General correspondence 1958 (Box 32)
      [32-16b]
    - Correspondence with John Goormaghtigh
      - 1957 (Box 32)
        [32-19]
      - 1957-1958 (Box 32)
        [32-18]
      - 1958-1960 (Box 32)
        [32-17]
    - Correspondence with Lilly Endowment 1955-1956 (Box 32)
      [32-20a]
    - Correspondence with Earhart Foundation 1956 (Box 32)
      [32-20b]
    - Executive Committee material (Box 33)
      - 1958-1960 (Box 33)
        [33-1]
      - 1955-1958, 2 folders (Box 33)
        [33-2; 32-3]
      - 1955-1961 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence with Ford Foundation 1957-1958 (Box 33)
      [33-5]
    - Addresses of members and membership lists (Box 33)
      [33-6]
    - Correspondence with Asia Foundation 1957-1958 (Box 33)
      [33-7a]
    - Correspondence with Carnegie Corporation 1955-1956 (Box 33)
      [33-7b]
    - Budget material 1956-1959 (Box 33)
      [33-8]
    - Constitution and other documents (Box 33)
      [33-9a]
    - Creole Foundation material 1958 (Box 33)
      [33-9b]
    - Minutes of Council meetings 1955-1961 (Box 33)
      [33-10]
    - Circular letters 1955-1957 (Box 33)
      [33-13]
    - Circular letters 1958-1960 (Box 33)
      [33-12]
    - Circular letters 1958-1962 (Box 33)
      [33-11]
  - Michigan Joint Legislative Committee on Reorganization of the State Government, Citizens Advisory Committee to (Box 18)
    - 1948, 1950-1952 (Box 18)
      [18-11]
    - 1950-1951 (Box 18)
      [18-7]
    - 1950-1952, 2 folders (Box 18)
      [18-9; 18-10]
    - Recommendations 1951 (Box 18)
      [18-8a]
  - Michigan Mutual Liability Company (sponsor of James K. Pollock's wartime radio broadcasts) 1941-1943 (Box 18)
    [18-8b]
  - Milan, International Conference on Underdeveloped Areas 1954 (Box 18)
    [18-12a]
  - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    [18-12b]
  - Moyco Press 1944-1946 (Box 18)
    [18-12c]
  - National War College 1946-1949 (Box 18)
    [18-16a]
  - "Nuffield College Report," 1941-1944 (Box 18)
    [18-16b]
  - Occupied Areas. Commission on the Occupied Areas-American Council on Education
    - 1948-1951, 2 folders (Box 18)
      [18-17; 18-19]
    - 1949-1950 (Box 18)
      [18-18]
    - Minutes 1948-1951 (Box 18)
      [18-20]
    - 1947-1950 (Box 19)
      [19-1]
    - Harold E. Snyder 1948-1951 (Box 19)
      [19-2]
  - Occupied Countries, Advisory Committee on Cultural and Educational Relations with the Occupied Countries-American Council on Education 1949 (Box 19)
    [19-4]
  - Outside Employment, University of Michigan Committee on 1954 (Box 19)
    [19-5a]
  - Panel on Governmental Affairs and Social Science 1950 (Box 19)
    [19-5b]
  - Pennsylvania Ambassador 1952 (Box 19)
    [19-6]
  - Political Behavior Studies 1949-1950 (Box 19)
    [19-7a]
  - Presidential Inauguration 1953 (Box 19)
    [19-7b]
  - Presidential Election Study of 1952, 1949-1952 (Box 19)
    [19-8]
  - Salaries, Faculty
    - 1941-1943, 1946 (Box 19)
      [19-10]
    - 1947-1948 (Box 19)
      [19-9]
  - Social Sciences, proposed Institute of, U-M 1941-1943 (Box 19)
    [19-11]
  - Social Science Research Council, Conference on Political Behavior August 1949 (Box 19)
    [19-12]
  - Stanford University, James K. Pollock teaching at 1947 (Box 19)
    [19-12b]
  - Subversive organization/House Un-American Activities Committee 1953 (Box 19)
    [19-12c]
  - United States Department of Labor, Wage and Hour Division, 3 folders (Box 19)
    [19-17; 19-18; 19-19]
  - University of Michigan
    - Advisory Board on University Policies 1943-1944 (Box 19)
      [19-13]
    - Economic Status of the Faculty, reports prepared by the U-M Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs 1945, 6 folders (Box 20)
      [20-2; 20-3; 20-4; 20-5; 20-6; 20-7]
    - Lecture Committee
      - 1941-1952 (Box 20)
        [20-17]
      - 1953 (Box 20)
        [20-16]
      - 1954 (Box 20)
        [20-15]
      - 1955 (Box 20)
        [20-14]
      - 1956-1957 (Box 20)
        [20-12]
      - 1957-1961 (Box 20)
        [20-13]
    - Research Club 1943-1954 (Box 20)
      [20-11]
    - Salary and Wage Adjustments 1943-1944 (Box 20)
      [20-1]
- Research Files 1920s-1960, 4 linear feet
  Research Files (1920s-1960; 4 linear ft.) is the title given to a group of research files on topics pertaining to Michigan politics and government and state election studies. This series does not represent the total of Pollock's research interests as other materials will be found in the European Election Studies series described below.
  - Government and Politics
    - Unicameral state legislatures 1934-1960 (Box 33)
      [33-14]
    - Administrative organization in Michigan 1936, 1941-1942, 1954 (Box 33)
      [33-15]
    - Michigan civil service 1960-1968 (Box 33)
      [33-16]
    - Michigan Civil Service Study Commission 1934-1960 (Box 33)
      (include James K. Pollock speeches and written contributions)
      [33-17]
    - Michigan Civil Service Study Commission 1940-1960 (Box 33)
      [33-18]
    - American political parties 1920s-1930s (Box 34)
      [34-1]
    - National party chairmen 1926, 2 folders (Box 34)
      [34-2; 34-3]
    - National party chairmen-manuscript of James K. Pollock study 1926 (Box 34)
      [34-4]
    - National Labor Relations Board elections at Ford Motor Company 1941 (Box 34)
      [34-5]
    - Voting behavior in America, pre-1950 (Box 34)
      [34-6]
    - Absentee voting (include James K. Pollock manuscript) (Box 34)
      [34-7]
    - Initiative and referendum-general material (Box 34)
      [34-8]
    - Initiative and referendum in Michigan 1940, 3 folders (Box 34)
      [34-9; 34-10; 34-11]
    - Campaign expenditure regulation (include James K. Pollock testimony given in 1952)
      - 1950-1961 (Box 34)
        [34-12]
      - 1928-1952 (Box 34)
        [34-13]
      - 1936-1963 (Box 34)
        [34-14]
    - Federal Corrupt Practices Act
      - General 1928 (Box 35)
        [35-7]
      - General 1929 (Box 35)
        [35-6]
      - General 1930-1940, 3 folders (Box 35)
        [35-1; 35-2; 35-3]
      - General 1940-1942 (Box 35)
        [35-5]
      - Nye Committee hearings 1931 (Box 35)
        [35-4]
    - 18-year old vote 1942-1954 (Box 35)
      [35-8]
  - Michigan elections
    - Population and electorate for Michigan by counties 1928-1940 (Box 35)
      [35-9]
    - Participation in Michigan elections 1928-1940 (Box 35)
      [35-10]
    - Michigan direct primary
      - 1941-1942, 3 folders (Box 35)
        [35-11; 35-13; 35-16]
      - 1941-1942 (seminar paper) (Box 35)
        [35-12]
      - Data sheets 1941-1942, 2 folders (Box 35)
        [35-14; 35-17]
      - "The Direct Primary in Michigan, 1909-1938" James K. Pollock manuscript, ca. 1941-1942 (Box 35)
        [35-15]
    - Michigan parties and nominations (student papers, etc.) 1938-1940 (Box 36)
      [36-1]
    - Party organization in Michigan 1939-1941 (Box 36)
      [36-2]
    - Party organization in Michigan (student papers) 1939-1941 (Box 36)
      [36-3]
    - Data sheets re Michigan elections 1908-1935, 3 folders (Box 36)
      [36-4; 36-6; 36-7]
    - Master data tape re Michigan elections 1908-1935 (Box 36)
      [36-5]
    - Election data 1910-1934
      (arranged by name of county)
      - Alcona (Box 36)
        [36-8]
      - Alger (Box 36)
        [36-9]
      - Alpena (Box 36)
        [36-10]
      - Calhoun (Box 36)
        [36-11]
      - Cass (Box 36)
        [36-12]
      - Genesee (Box 36)
        [36-13]
      - Ingham (Box 36)
        [36-14]
      - Kalamazoo (Box 36)
        [36-15]
      - Kent (Box 36)
        [36-16]
      - Lenawee (Box 36)
        [36-17]
      - Macomb (Box 36)
        [36-18]
      - Muskegon (Box 36)
        [36-19]
      - Oakland (Box 36)
        [36-20]
      - Saginaw (Box 37)
        [37-1]
      - St. Clair (Box 37)
        [37-2]
      - Washtenaw (Box 37)
        [37-3]
      - Wayne (Box 37)
        [37-4]
    - Election data-Michigan State Representatives
      - 1922 (Box 37)
        [37-5]
      - 1924 (Box 37)
        [37-6]
      - 1926 (Box 37)
        [37-7]
      - 1928 (Box 37)
        [37-8]
      - 1930 (Box 37)
        [37-9]
      - 1932 (Box 37)
        [37-10]
      - 1934 (Box 37)
        [37-11]
    - Election data-Michigan State Senators
      - 1910-1934 (Box 37)
        [37-12]
      - 1922 (Box 37)
        [37-14]
      - 1924 (Box 37)
        [37-15]
      - 1926 (Box 37)
        [37-16]
      - 1928 (Box 37)
        [37-17]
      - 1930 (Box 37)
        [37-18]
      - 1932 (Box 37)
        [37-19]
      - 1934 (Box 37)
        [37-20]
    - Election data-Circuit Court Judges 1911-1935 (Box 37)
      [37-13]
    - Election data-Miscellaneous (Box 37)
      [37-21]
    - James K. Pollock paper: "Voting Behavior in Ann Arbor" (Box 37)
      [37-22]
    - Pollock-Eldersveld paper: "Michigan Politics in Transition" (1930-1940) (Box 37)
      [37-23]
    - Michigan Election Commission 1931, 2 folders (Box 37)
      [37-25; 37-26]
    - Michigan Election Commission 1929 (Box 37)
      [37-27]
- Governmental Public Service 1948-1968, 18 linear feet
  James K. Pollock was widely respected for his knowledge of the workings of government on both the state and national level. Because of that he was selected to work on specific problems of government or with specific agencies. Files from these activities, most of which took place after World War II, have been grouped together in the series, Governmental Public Service (1948-1968; 18 linear ft.). This series does not include Pollock's work in Germany after the war. Nor does it include his service with the Michigan Civil Service Study Commission which was a series of files donated to the library many years prior to the major accessioning of Pollock papers in 1969. The subseries under Governmental Public Service consist of Hoover Commission, the Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, the Michigan Constitutional Convention of 1962-1963, the Citizens Conference on State Legislatures, and the Governor's Special Commission on Legislative Compensation. There is also a miscellaneous topical subseries on issues of congressional organization and reapportionment, among other issues.
  - Hoover Commission 1948-1949
    - Personnel directory (Box 38)
      [38-1]
    - Correspondence
      - Acheson, Dean (Box 38)
        [38-2a]
      - Aiken, George D. (Box 38)
        [38-2b]
      - Brassor, Frances P. (Box 38)
        [38-3]
      - Brown, Clarence J. (Box 38)
        [38-4a]
      - Fleming, Arthur S. (Box 38)
        [38-4b]
      - Forrestal, James (Box 38)
        [38-4c]
      - Hoover, Herbert (Box 38)
        [38-5]
      - Kennedy, Joseph P. (Box 38)
        [38-6a]
      - Manasco, Carter (Box 38)
        [38-6b]
      - McClellan, John L. (Box 38)
        [38-6c]
      - Mead, George H. (Box 38)
        [38-6d]
      - Mitchell, Sidney A. (Box 38)
        [38-6e]
      - Rowe, James, Jr. (Box 38)
        [38-7a]
      - Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Box 38)
        [38-7b]
    - General Correspondence, A-L (Box 38)
      [38-8]
    - General Correspondence, K-Z (Box 38)
      [38-9]
    - Topical file I
      - Appropriation allotment material 1948-1949 (Box 38)
        [38-10]
      - Conference on the Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government April 24-26, 1948 (Box 38)
        [38-11]
      - Congressional material (Box 38)
        [38-12]
      - Corporations (Box 38)
        [38-13a]
      - District of Columbia (Box 38)
        [38-13b]
      - Council of Economic Advisers (Box 38)
        [38-13c]
      - Committee on Expenditures (Box 38)
        [38-13d]
      - Federal Security Agency (Box 38)
        [38-14a]
      - Printing; Procedures (Box 38)
        [38-14b]
      - Task Force Reports (Box 38)
        [38-14c]
      - Public Relations activities (Box 38)
        [38-15a]
      - Status reports 1948-1949 (Box 38)
        [38-15b]
      - Submissions to Congress (Box 38)
        [38-16a]
      - Submissions to Commission (Box 38)
        [38-16b]
    - Clippings, 3 folders (Box 38)
      [38-17; 38-18; 38-19]
    - Topical File II
      - Agendas, notes, and papers, 2 folders (Box 38)
        [38-20; 38-21]
      - Agendas, notes, and papers (Box 39)
        [39-1]
      - Vouchers (Box 39)
        [39-2]
      - Pollock materials, 2 folders (Box 39)
        [39-3; 39-4]
      - Federal Works Agency, 2 folders (Box 39)
        [39-5; 39-6]
      - Housing (Box 39)
        [39-7]
      - Information program (Box 39)
        [39-8a]
      - Justice Department (Box 39)
        [39-8b]
      - Memoranda (Box 39)
        [39-8c]
      - Memoranda (Pollock-Heady) 1948-1949 (Box 39)
        [39-9]
      - Minutes 1947-1949 (Box 39)
        [39-10]
      - Miscellanea (Box 39)
        [39-11]
      - Nomenclature 1948 (Box 39)
        [39-12a]
      - Press Conferences 1948 (Box 39)
        [39-12b]
      - Political Scientists in Commission 1949 (Box 39)
        [39-12c]
      - Plans and Suggestion (Box 39)
        [39-13]
      - Press releases 1947-1948, 2 folders (Box 39)
        [39-14; 39-15]
    - Topical file III
      - Agriculture Committee
        - Drafts of reports 1948 (Box 39)
          [39-16]
        - General 1948, 2 folders (Box 39)
          [39-17; 39-18]
      - Budgeting and Accounting 1948-1949 (Box 39)
        [39-19]
      - Business Enterprises in Governmental Reform
        - General, 4 folders (Box 40)
          [40-1; 40-2; 40-4; 40-6]
        - Draft of commission report February 8, 1949 (Box 40)
          [40-3]
        - Draft report on Federal Lending, Guarantee and Insurance Agencies December 9, 1948 (Box 40)
          [40-5]
      - Commerce Department Reform
        - 1949 (Box 40)
          [40-7]
        - 1948 (include transportation) (Box 40)
          [40-8]
        - 1947-1948 (include National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics) (Box 40)
          [40-9]
      - General Services Committee, 2 folders (Box 40)
        [40-10; 40-11]
      - Foreign Affairs Committee
        - General (Box 40)
          [40-12]
        - Draft of commission report (Box 40)
          [40-13]
        - 1948 (Box 40)
          [40-14]
      - General Management of Executive Branch
        - Overall report (Box 40)
          [40-15]
        - Draft report January 5, 1949 (Box 40)
          [40-16]
        - Draft report January 13, 1949, 2 folders (Box 40)
          [40-17; 40-18]
        - 1948-1949 (Box 40)
          [40-19]
        - General (Box 40)
          [40-20]
        - General, 3 folders (Box 41)
          [41-1; 41-2; 41-3]
      - Interior (Dept. of)
        - Public Works (Box 41)
          [41-4]
        - Natural Resources, 3 folders (Box 41)
          [41-5; 41-6; 41-7]
      - Labor (Dept. of) (Box 41)
        [41-8]
      - Governmental Medical Services, 2 folders (Box 41)
        [41-9; 41-10]
      - National Security Organization (Box 41)
        [41-11]
      - Personnel Management
        - General, 4 folders (Box 41)
          [41-12; 41-13; 41-14; 41-15]
        - Project on Federal Personnel Management, preliminary report, 2 folders (Box 41)
          [41-16; 41-17]
      - Post Office (Box 41)
        [41-18]
      - Independent Regulatory Agencies (Box 42)
        [42-1]
      - Transport Regulatory Commission (Box 42)
        [42-2]
      - Federal-State Relations
        - Papers include report on "The Developmental Powers in the United States" (Box 42)
          [42-3]
        - General (Box 42)
          [42-4]
        - Bane Report (Box 42)
          [42-5]
      - Overseas Administration
        - General (Box 42)
          [42-6]
        - "Federal Activities in the Territories" (Box 42)
          [42-7]
      - Research in the Federal Government (Box 42)
        [42-8]
      - Public Welfare-Social Security, Education, 2 folders (Box 42)
        [42-9; 42-10]
      - Indian Affairs (Box 42)
        [42-11]
      - Treasury Department (Box 42)
        [42-12]
      - Veterans Administration (Box 42)
        [42-13]
    - Concluding Report
      - Published copies (Box 42)
        [42-14]
      - Galley proofs, 4 folders (Box 42)
        [42-15; 42-16; 42-17; 42-18]
      - Galley proofs, 6 folders (Box 43)
        [43-1 to 43-6]
    - Miscellaneous
      - History of Federal Reorganization 1920-1947 (Box 43)
        [43-7]
      - Reports, comments, bills, and miscellanea re HC 1948-1949, 4 folders (Box 43)
        [43-8 to 43-11]
      - Lecture notes: "The Executive in Policy Formation," 1949 (Box 43)
        [43-12]
      - Reports relating to the Hoover Commission (Box 43)
        (include Commerce Dept. section of the report)
        [43-13]
      - Excerpts from Pimlott manuscript, "Public Relations in Government" (Box 43)
        [43-14]
      - Miscellaneous (Box 43)
        [43-15]
      - Notes for a speech on the HC at the Detroit Economic Club 1949 (Box 43)
        [43-16]
      - News clippings and miscellaneous (Box 43)
        [43-17]
      - Outline and text of James K. Pollock's speech on the HC delivered to the American Society for Public Administration March 12, 1948 (Box 43)
        [43-18]
      - Hoover Commission-Administrative Services 1948-1949 (Box 43)
        [43-19]
      - Speeches and speech materials (Box 43)
        [43-20]